entertime.net 2001-08-03

# EnterTime.Net Privacy

**EnterTime.Net Privacy Policy**

Effective 9 September 2000

  * Our Commitment To Privacy
  * The Information We Collect
  * How We Use Information
  * Our Commitment To Data Security
  * How To Access Or Correct Your Information
  * How To Contact Us

**Our Commitment To Privacy:**

Privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**The Information We Collect:**

  * The types of information we collect are:
  * Information that you give us to set up an account: 
    * Name
    * Email address
    * User name Password 
  * Additional information that you give us to become a customer: 

    * Address
    * Credit/Debit Card Information
  * Information Collected Automatically: 

    * The type of web browser you are using 
    * The IP address assigned to the computer you are using
    * Details of requests for pages from our web server
    * Cookies we store on your computer 
    * Cryptographic information required for secure communication
  * Business transactions we have with customers: 

    * Information that customers give us
    * Transaction logs

**How We Use the Information:  
**   
We never use the personally identifiable information that you provide to us online in ways that are unrelated to the primary purposes for which you provided that information.

Your information will be kept strictly confidential.

Account and billing information is used for communications that are part of the service, for administrative purposes, and for billing your credit card.

We use non-identifying, aggregate information to better design our website and network infrastructure. Cookies may be used to facilitate your navigation of our site.

**Our Commitment To Data Security:**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect and maintain online by logging in as Administrator. You can delete all your personally identifiable information that we maintain online by logging in as Administrator, selecting Close Account, and responding affirmatively to the email that will be sent to your Administrator's email address.

**How To Contact Us:**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please use the Feedback link provided throughout our site for the quickest response. If your questions or concerns are not urgent, you may send email to [info@EnterTime.Net](mailto:info@EnterTime.Net). You may call us at 972-783-8770 to leave voice mail, but our business model for providing this inexpensive, efficient service precludes relying on such high-cost, inefficient means of communication.
